kennedyspacecenter.com 2015-12-07

# Kennedy Space Center | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
The website www.delawarenorth.com (the “Web Site”) is operated by Delaware North Companies, Incorporated, or its affiliate (collectively, “Delaware North”). Delaware North’s online privacy policy tells you about the information Delaware North, its subsidiaries or affiliates collect through the services available on the Web Site and in any other way, including but not limited to, your participation in our promotions or customer surveys. In addition, it explains how we use that information and how you can opt out of certain uses of information we may collect. By using our services, providing your personal information and/or accessing our Web Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this statement, as modified from time to time by us. If this privacy policy is not acceptable to you, please do not use this Web Site or provide your personal information. If we decide to materially change our privacy policy, we will post a new statement on our Web Site. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy policy whenever you visit this Web Site for any updates or changes. 

**Information About You**  
We collect several types of information about you. We collect "personal information," which generally is information such as your first and last name, home address and e-mail address that can be used to identify you individually. We also collect "non-personal information," which is information about you that does not itself identify you individually. Examples of non-personal information include age range and gender. We also collect "aggregate information," which is information that helps us understand how people use our Web Site or our services, for example, which pages are visited. The information we collect depends on what services you use on our Web Site or otherwise. The following is a more detailed explanation of these types of information as well as when and how we collect and use them. 

**Registration and Transactional Data**  
When you register or join our mailing list on our Web Site, we may collect various kinds of personal information, including your first and last name, e-mail address, home address, home phone number, personal interests and preferred vacation/leisure destinations. We also collect and store access information related to your account, including user name and user password. When you make purchases from our Web Site, we may collect purchasing information such as information relating to product orders, shipping address(es) and credit card information. 

**Surveys**  
From time to time we may post surveys on our Web Site or invite you to participate in our surveys. The surveys may request demographic information (such as age range, gender, areas of interest and familiarity with Delaware North or our products and services), your personal information, consumer preferences, and customer feedback. Participation in these requests is completely voluntary. With each request, you will have the choice of whether or not to disclose information. Such survey information will be used individually and in its aggregate to improve the overall experience on the Web Site, to improve the guest experience at one of our owned and/or operated locations, provide you with promotional and other marketing offers and to improve the goods and services we offer to you. 

**Customer Service Correspondence**  
We may collect personal information that identifies you individually, such as your first and last name, home address, e-mail address, phone number, fax number when you submit comments, questions or suggestions to our Corporate Communications Department. 

**On-Line Forums**  
Our Web Site may have chat rooms, discussion boards, online forums and other interactive technologies that allow individual comments and messages to be tied to a user's name or e-mail address. Any information you post in such forums is public information and Delaware North cannot control what uses third parties may make of personal information you share in such forums. You should exercise caution before disclosing personal information. 

**Use of Your Personal and Non-Personal Information**  
Except as disclosed in this privacy policy, we do not sell, rent, lease or disclose information that identifies you individually or makes it possible for other parties to contact you directly without your consent. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we only share your personal information with other Delaware North entities and third parties who are acting on our behalf for the uses described below. Such Delaware North entities and third parties are bound by confidentiality agreements requiring them to protect this data. We may, however, use, sell, disclose or otherwise dispose of personal information we collect in the following circumstances: 

**Data integrity**  
Delaware North processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this privacy policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed in connection with the uses set out in this privacy policy. 

**Internal Analysis and Promotions**  
We may use information about you for statistical, design or operational purposes such as to estimate our audience size, to measure aggregate traffic patterns and/or to and understand demographics, customer interest, consumer insights, purchasing and other trends among our users and customers. We may also use your personal information for the marketing and/or promotion of Delaware North, our subsidiaries and/or affiliated companies, including their products and services. Additionally, we may use your information to confirm a reservation, respond to inquiries on the Web Site such as "Contact Us", "Testimonials", "Send a Web page to a Friend" or event planning. We may outsource all of these tasks to third parties on a confidential basis. If you do not want to receive promotional materials from us or the third parties we have engaged, please send your opt-out request to [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com). 

**Transaction Processing**  
We may use your personal information to create a convenient and easy-to-use online reservation service or shopping process that includes an online "shopping cart" that allows you to track selected services or products and proceed through purchase. We may also share transactional information with entities as is necessary to process credit card payments or other purchasing or delivery systems. 

**Offers from Subsidiaries and Affiliates**  
We may send you (or arrange to have sent to you) our (or our subsidiaries’ and affiliates’) marketing and promotional information. We do not share your personal information with unrelated outside third parties unless such disclosure is required for transaction processing as mentioned above. If you do not want to receive these materials, please email your opt-out request to [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com). 

**Legal Requirement**  
We may disclose personal information:  
(a) to conform with the law, respond to claims or comply with legal process served on Delaware North (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order);  
(b) to enforce or apply our policies or agreements (including to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us);  
(c) to protect and defend our or our users’ rights or property, the Web Site, our employees, users or the public, including fraudulent, abusive or unlawful use of our Web Site; or  
(d) if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.  

**Choice**  
Delaware North will not use or share your personal information in ways unrelated to the uses described above without first notifying you and offering a choice. We will also provide you the opportunity to opt-out at any time of certain or all contact from Delaware North. If you have any difficulty exercising your choices, please send your request to [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com). 

**Company Sale**  
Information collected through our Web Site is considered a trade secret of Delaware North. As the owner of such information, we may disclose or sell such information as an asset of the company in conjunction with the sale to a third party of our company or a portion of our assets. 

**Aggregate Information**  
We collect aggregate information about you and your use of our Web Site whenever you visit us online (See “Information About You” above). For instance, we may collect various forms of "click stream" information such as entry and exit points for our Web Site (i.e., referring URLs or domains), site traffic statistics, page views, impressions, and operating system and browser type. In addition, when you request pages on our Web Site, our servers automatically log your IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the internet. We also use third-party software that tracks traffic directed to the Web Site from affiliate web sites and the purchases that result from this traffic. This information is aggregated and is not tied to an individual purchase. This aggregate information generally will not identify you or be correlated to you individually for external purposes. We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all aggregate information provided that such information does not reveal your identity. When we share such information with other companies, it is not traceable to any particular user, and will not be used to contact you. If we do correlate any aggregate information to you, such information will be treated like any other personal information under this statement. 

**Tracking Tools**  
We and our third-party vendors collect personal and other information about users over time and across different websites when you use this Web Site or the services offered on the Web Site. We use browser-based "cookies", users' IP addresses, and other technologies such as "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs," or similar technologies to help us and third parties obtain information about your visits to the Web Site, deliver online and mobile ads and content for us and others specific to your interests, process your purchases or requests, and/or to analyze your visiting patterns, measure the effectiveness of our and others’ advertising, monitor traffic patterns on this Web Site, and to optimize and enhance your online experience on our Web Site. "Cookies" are pieces of information stored within your computer’s or device’s Internet browser that automatically identify your browser to our server whenever you interact with the Web Site. Such technology is a common feature of many web sites and is necessary in order for certain features of our site to function properly or in order to provide an online service to you. We also use cookies to help us understand the content that you are shown while visiting our Web Site. We may combine information which we obtain through the use of cookies with other information, including a unique identifier we have assigned to you, or with information we obtain from third party sources. 

**Managing Tracking Tools**  
You may customize the browser settings to notify you when a cookie is sent or to disable cookies altogether. Please check the Help feature on your browser for instructions on how to make these adjustments. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of the Web Site’s essential features, we recommend that you allow them on your browser. If you block or otherwise disable cookies, you will not be able to hold selections in a shopping cart when you leave our Website without checking out, or use any services on our Web Site that require you to sign in. Some of the tracking we have described herein will continue even if you disable or block cookies. Your browser may also have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals. 

**Interest-Based Online Ads**  
From time to time we and other advertisers may engage in interest-based advertising provided by vendors in order to deliver advertisements and personalized content that may be of interest to you. To the extent third-party vendors use cookies or other technologies to perform these services for us or other advertisers, we do not control the use of this technology or the resulting information, and are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. Ads may be delivered to you based on your online or mobile behavior (on our and other web sites), your search activity, your geographic location or other information. For example, if you make a reservation on this Web Site, you may later see our ad on another website or on mobile platforms. You may also see third-party ads on this Web Site, other websites, or mobile apps, based on your visits to, and activities on this Web Site, other websites and mobile apps. Third parties may use technologies to track your activities over time and across mobile apps to deliver you advertising and content that may be of interest to you. By visiting http://www.aboutads.info/choices, you can learn more about interest-based advertising and opt out of having your on-line behavior tracked to tailor content or advertising to you. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
Please be aware that we provide links to third-party web sites as a service to our users, and that we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those pages. Please note that these web sites' privacy policies may differ from those of Delaware North. We encourage you to review and understand their privacy practices before providing them with information. 

**Children**  
Our Web Site is intended for a general audience. However, it is not designed nor intended to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. To respect the privacy of children and to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information on this Web Site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online. 

**Security**  
Delaware North is committed to safeguarding and securing your personal information. To maintain data accuracy, prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of, and ensure the appropriate use of your personal information, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures. When we ask for credit card data, it is transferred over a Secured Sockets Layer (SSL) line provided you are using an SSL-enabled browser such as Microsoft Internet Explorer. This ensures that your information is encrypted as it travels through the Internet. This secure mode is enabled before any such information is transmitted from your computer. You will know that you are in “secure mode” when the padlock or key icon in the lower-right-hand or lower-left-hand corner of the computer screen appears in the locked position. In addition, when accessing a secure server, the first characters of the web Site address will change from “http” to “https.” 

**Opting Out of Promotional Materials**  
As noted above, we may use your e-mail address and other contact information provided to us through the Web Site to send promotional materials to you. If you do not want to receive such promotional information, you can change your privacy preference and remove yourself from our e-mail list at any time. 

**Access and Accuracy**  
Delaware North strives to keep your personal information accurate. We will provide you with access to your personal information, including making reasonable efforts to provide you with online access to your subscription or registration data so that you may review, update or correct your information at the Site. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections. To access your personal information, return to the web page where you originally entered the Site and follow the instructions on that web page. If you cannot access your information on the web page, please telephone us at (716) 858-5000 for assistance, or send you request to [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com). We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, would be extremely impractical or for which access is not otherwise required. If you are registered with our Web Site, please sign in and use the preference form at “Your Account” to access your information. If you have NOT completed the registration process, please e-mail your request to [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com). If you would like to change or delete your information you have provided us, please email us at [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com)or telephone us at (716) 858-5000 as ask for Corporate Communications. Notwithstanding any preference that you select, we may contact you from time to time to provide services that you have requested or for customer service matters, such as responding to service-related inquiries, updating our policies or notifying you of changes to existing services. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of your information, or if you need help changing or deleting your information, you can e-mail us at [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com)or send a letter to: 

Delaware North Companies, Incorporated  
40 Fountain Plaza  
Buffalo, NY 14202  
ATTN: Corporate Communications  
Effective Date: February 26, 2014  

**California Privacy Policy**  
As a California resident you have the legal right to request from businesses with whom you have an established business relationship, (1) a list of the categories of personal information, such as your name, address, email address and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please email [webinfo@dncinc.com](mailto:webinfo@dncinc.com), or mail your written request to Delaware North Companies, Incorporated, 40 Fountain Plaza, Buffalo, New York 14202, Attn: Corporate Communications, with a reference to California Disclosure Information.
